[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Hey.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Is that your analysis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Like where we are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "And what can you do about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "Well, I don't think that I need to be prepared for it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 72, "question": "Do you regret that you've got into bed with the super PACs, even though you won't admit you have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "Well --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Do you believe Mitt Romney when he says that he's paid at least 13 percent for the last 10 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "JJS", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "I'll say he's setting an entirely new precedent.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"], "PERCENT": ["13 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "Do you regret that Joe Biden used that particular phrase?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Listen, I know what the vice president was saying.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe Biden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "It's getting exciting, isn't it, this election?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "Well, I look forward -- I look forward to seeing you along the way, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "Why would you think that President Obama would want his citizens in his own country to be second class?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "Well, Obama is a global guy.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "You don't obviously believe that, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Not only do I believe it but Obama says it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tunisia", "Egypt"]}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "What on earth do you base that on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Well, first of all, the radical Muslims have come to power in Tunisia and Egypt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "I mean, that is an absolute load of filly, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Well, first of all, we're talking about Obama's motives.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["Egypt", "Egypt"]}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ":", "RB", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "Would you be sending in American troops in Tehran?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "Well, of course -- well, no, no, for starters, look, Obama supported the protesters in Egypt very happily when they were demanding democracy in Egypt.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tehran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "That's not really the actions of a guy who's not worried, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "No, I think we have to make an important distinction here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "ORGAN: Where do you get the fact that he detests my country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Well, let's start with something simple.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "Any initial thoughts?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "I -- it's rather troubling to me to agree with you on everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJR", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Why on earth would any American president actively want to put his citizens into more debt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "JJ", "MD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "RBR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "Because if American citizens and if our children and grandchildren are saddled with more debt, at some point they're going to have to pay that money back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "Dinesh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "Well, you're attacking -- you're attacking a complete straw man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "You think Colonel Gadhafi has only killed -- before he was killed himself, he only killed 250 Libyans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "He only killed 250 Libyans before Obama initiated the use of force, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Colonel Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Syria"]}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "How do you explain the double standard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "I'm just about to come to Syria.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", ":", "DT", ",", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 392, "question": "What's crazy about them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "ILLETTE: -- No, no --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "You were one of his, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "This is a bad move, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "That can happen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Should he have that tiny amount of body fat?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "It's a measurement like body weight or BMX or BMI.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "What is different about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "You know, we call it muscle confusion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Just scoff hot dogs all day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "There's no one size fits all here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "When he came to you for the first time, what shape was he in then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "He was in great shape when he started.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Is that where they come together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Well, when I'm there, it's a very bipartisan affair.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "A good payer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "Payer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Does he always pay up on time and give you a good tip?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "There's no payment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "How come he gets a freebie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "They all do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "What are the things I should just forget about doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Stop being attached to the outcome.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "Does he know after all the commitment he's given you, the 100 percent dedication, that you still haven't given him his vote?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "We never discuss it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "Did you think anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "Are you just one of life's naturally unlucky guys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "CD", "IN", "NN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "Unfortunately I have been in a few accidents in my life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "Although I think one of you was unconscious, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "That would be me, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]